Over the ruined city, a colossal Grade-S gate opens and the Shadow Legion deploys.
Gate response spikes, briefly exposing an offline recalibration HUD.
The first soul-pool condenses. Secure a stable hunt loop and time the extraction.
`Bind the legion` misfired repeatedly. Correct command and switch to one retry loop.
Advance to the node front. Secure a micro-node to claim territory control.
Control starts to fluctuate. Force summon auto-redeploy and load-shedding commands.
Major engagement phase. Mass forces expand along the pressure line.
Trade loss chain triggers stagger state. Execute a short heal burst, then snapshot rollback.
Shadow Swap and Monarch Domain open an inversion point for a counter-strike window.
Mass losses and suppression phase. Retreat and recompose repeatedly as losing odds rise.
Approaching the survival floor. Using Void Devour decides the fate of this clash.
Entering boss apex. Execute compression timing while resistance lines of the S-grade core fluctuate.
Critical fail pivot: resolve error instantly with a shrine-return impulse and pause next-phase deployment.
Collect into the return channel and settle persistent-growth rewards regardless of win/lose state.